Name: Gabriel De La Cruz
Role: Info Editor Developer
Fav language: Python

### Must Have (We NEED these to demo)
- [ ] As an editing developer, I want to save info, so that it can be easily accessed without leaving the app open
- [ ] As an editing developer, I want to make an abstract array, so that I can control the information without being limited by an array size.
 
### Nice to Have (If we have time)
- [ ] As an editing developer, I want to make it run fast, so that info is saved in real time and doesn’t rely on leaving the API open.
- [ ] As a tester, I want it to be mostly user friendly, so that anybody can pick it up and edit their info.

