Name: Xavier Rosado
Role: Designer
Favorite Programming Language: Python

## Must Have (We NEED these to demo)
- [ ] As a Designer, I want to have a login feature, so that users can have an account to login with.
- [ ] As a Designer, I want to code the login feature simple, so that it can be a quicker code and be more legible.
 

### Nice to Have (If we have time)
- [ ] As a Designer, I want my code to run quick, so that it doesn't have slowdown issues.
- [ ] As a Tester, I want to see all code run together, so that the main code can just be one and be something where the user can quit once done.
